Jhal
[Music]
that scientist
Ajay
Jhal
Hello Hello Friends our channel show today
Bareilly Mandal Vice Chancellor Stock and time finally you can
subscribe and this topic in which first of all
it was a lot of consolidation for yesterday but if you look at it, then
here you will see
stop stop stop stop and
this is what you are doing and from here you
could not stand on the quality but on this web store anti we have
a use upside qualification if that topic is
235 here please share with your
friends and family but also that
in 24 loop the next actor is this
organization Madwa in 2015 on Friday and 7.30
like Shiva is on one side after that you will see
retail katwa here in this one so here
we only but because it has back side
and we can give it our
quick heal proposal more so on Monday we
can give a little bit of Mike Proctor this relationship on it and now
subscribe to Z2 and
subscribe a little bit if your profit is
Jindal Steel now we are in this for this problem
And looking at this, August stock here
shift club skin so there is one more in this and for this
subscribe us and here towards the top of the next
and call 100
hey brother right now we have that urban tight
container inches we have one and if this 10 can be
used and if you daily
here we will give you a little bit till
it is
above 001 Kunti here illegal 35.8 1 minute
spot closes and because of this,
if we have 350 then with your husband we have
above 15 on this our channel today
in this video and if you and I are
learning to train live here with us then
you can change our group, if you want
support for your portfolio or
want a model portfolio juice and
want some more professional help for yourself then the
portfolio subscribe link is
in the description below that